[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sadiki_Topic01",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_TalkSage_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_TalkSage",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"It appeared to contain some kind of map.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Excellent, yes… I can make out the basic elements, but to decipher these words, I'll need samples of the desert tongue, the original language of the Blood of the Sands. \\n\\nWhere might we acquire such things?",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic01",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_MeetSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_MeetSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why are you in a cage?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "These... fanatical bastards believe anyone else in these ruins is a trespasser.\\n\\nLast time I checked, no one's had claim to this land for centuries, but they didn't want to hear that. Obsessed with finding some dusty old rock…",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic01a",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_FreeSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_FreeSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're out of your cage. I've upheld my end of the bargain.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Well done. I would have been tempted to give these brutes some payback, but you seem to have done the job well enough. \\n\\nI suppose it's now on me to uphold my end of our bargain.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic02",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This had better be good.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I'm in no position to champion any moral code, but this new cult claiming to be the Blood of the Sands - they are mad and dangerous. \\n\\nYou do realize what type of creature has been incubating in that egg for the last few millennia?",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic03",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You're not telling me the whole story.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Well, of course I'm not! There's not a soul in this desert who doesn't have secrets!\\n\\nComing from a family of superstitious fools who liked to say incantations over dusty old eggs, well, that's just one of the more shameful ones.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic04",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_HideSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_HideSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"But we can hide the egg here?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes. There's a vault. You'll have to clear a path through this rabble, however.\\n\\nOnce inside, place the egg on the pedestal and we'll seal the chamber door. That should keep it safe from lunatics like Malek.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic05",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_AmbushSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_AmbushSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We'll have to hide the egg somewhere else.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I don't know - it was a pretty short list of places I had in mind. We may have to come up with a new plan.\\n\\nFor now, I'll lead as many as I can out into the dunes, and then I'll circle back and catch up with you.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic06",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Have you been inside yet?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I have not. As you might imagine, I'm a bit hesitant about stepping back into that old life. The memories of that time are… uh, not pleasant.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic07",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_MeetSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_MeetSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What happened? You seemed fine outside.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "It's nothing. Just every so often I get some strange… flashes. Nothing to worry about - it'll pass.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic08",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“We must get the egg before they do.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "That we must. I believe I have a plan. \\n\\nDo you think you could create a diversion so I could sneak inside and find the egg? If you make enough noise, they should be distracted long enough so I can make off with it.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic09",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Sharif! Thank goodness you're alive! What happened?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I was looking for the egg chamber… someone snuck up on me, stealthy bastard… gave me quite a blow to the head. \\n\\nI remember being dragged... through the sands until I ended up here.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic10",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“It's finished. Malek is gone.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I can't imagine the horror. But the Devourers exact their own justice. They knew who was responsible for the destruction of the eggs. \\n\\nMalek's fate was sealed the moment he entered the Chamber of Shah Neshen.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic11",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkSharif",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“You're looking much better, Sharif!\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Thanks to you. And I've always been a fast healer. \\n\\nBut mostly I think a massive weight has been lifted off my shoulders.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic01",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkRima",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"A flattering one, I hope.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Hmm, perhaps the intrigue of wondering what I'll write is more valuable than the words themselves. \\n\\nThat will be especially true if we are to draw blades together and mix the melodies of our fates. That is your intent, yes?",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic02",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaSong_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaSong",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I am ready whenever you are.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Play the song here and we will gauge the magic of it. It should break the seal. \\n\\nInside is a sacred lute I have dreamt of playing for many years. With it, I will join you and we will compose legendary songs together.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic03",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaJoin_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaJoin",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So you'll join the Silver Crows?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, I have already spoken with Grace O'Malley, and I will return to her to confirm my commitment. \\n\\nFirst, however, I must spend some time with this beautiful lute. We will make enchanting music together. I will join you after.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic04",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkRima",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Did you learn anything else?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "A confirmation of your suspicions, I believe. Apparently, Malek was preaching in the streets after the awakening of Shah Neshen. \\n\\nHe believes the time of prophesy has arrived - that all the Devourers will soon awaken.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic05",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkRima",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“That's what I'm here for. Did you find a second egg?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Ah yes, well… in a way. Let me explain. \\n\\nThe locations of the last two eggs are vague, probably intentionally so. They left clues, but the exact locations are unclear.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic06",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkRima",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I'm glad it's over. How's Sharif?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "He had an epiphany of sorts. I have a feeling that our adventure together made him yearn for a life he thought he had left behind. \\n\\nHe seems like a new man.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic01",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkZander",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Speaking of ingredients, do you know a recipe to make a lion roar?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Make a lion roar? Haha, that’s not a request I thought I’d hear. You know I don’t eat meat but hmmm… I might have something in mind for a lion. \\n\\nHere, try this. That should work for what you want.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic02",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkZander",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Something like that. Are you hoping to join me?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Of course! Grace sent word for us to help. I would have arrived sooner, but her map was incredibly faulty!\\n\\nEverything was backwards! Ah wait. It was upside down. That makes so much more sense.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic03",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_MeetZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_MeetZander",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Glad to have you here. What's your plan?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Grace told me you were ambushed before, so Dog and I will keep that from happening again. \\n\\nWe will guard the entrance here, and make sure that nobody follows you in.",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic04",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_ZanderRuins_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_ZanderRuins",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“According to the map, another egg room should be here.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I see. Then it's just a matter of finding the door? \\n\\nHmm, what kind of door would it be? Something shaped like the one up there?",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic05",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkZander",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I did. But now we need to find the third.\"",
        "NPCResponse": "Pythagoras believed that the number three carries great power.\\n\\nI have a feeling there is something fateful about this third egg. Where will we find it?",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Jackal_Topic01",
<<<<<<< HEAD
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkJackal_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkJackal",
=======
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Can you understand me?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "…",
>>>>>>> PTR
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    }
]
